searchpluswin.com 2010-12-30

# Element Search + Win : search.elementskateboards.com

The Santa Barbara Group, LLC ("Santa Barbara") owns and operates a number of premier sites (the "Santa Barbara Sites") on the Web including Element Search + Win ("search.elementskateboards.com"). Santa Barbara is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user communities. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Santa Barbara may gather about individuals who visit the Santa Barbara Sites, how that information is used, and the Santa Barbara Sites' disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the Santa Barbara Sites, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links. Related to this, please also note that Santa Barbara provides certain user information to its sponsors and customers.

## Anonymous User Information

Each of the Santa Barbara Sites collects some anonymous information each time you visit them so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with the Santa Barbara Sites before we can collect this anonymous information. The Santa Barbara Sites do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or email address, in order for you to use the Santa Barbara Sites. The Santa Barbara Sites assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the Santa Barbara Site, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. Santa Barbara analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## Invite Your Friends and Win

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our sites, we ask you for your friend's name and email address. Santa Barbara will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the particular Santa Barbara Site. Santa Barbara does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time email sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input.

## Correspondence

If you contact Santa Barbara, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address.

## Third Party Information Gathering

The Santa Barbara Sites contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that Santa Barbara is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Cookies

Santa Barbara may set and access Santa Barbara or partner cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a Web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on the Santa Barbara Sites our visitors view and which Web browsers our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you within various Santa Barbara Sites in a way that may be linked to individual user information that you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site.

## Sharing

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of any Santa Barbara Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## Mergers; Business Transitions

In the event Santa Barbara goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

## Choice / Opt-out

We desire to keep you in control of the personal information you provide to us. Accordingly, you can review, correct, change or remove the personal registration information you provide to Santa Barbara and that Santa Barbara controls. In order to elect not to receive future communications from us, please email us at [info@santabarbaragroup.com](mailto:info@santabarbaragroup.com).

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places deemed appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use Individually Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

## Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Users under the age of 13)

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with Santa Barbara policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT:

  1. Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or
  2. Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties; It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers. Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to [info@santabarbaragroup.com](mailto:info@santabarbaragroup.com). You may also contact us by mail at Santa Barbara Group, LLC 2118 Wilshire Blvd. #1144, Santa Monica, CA 90403.
